I'm on a journey out to see the world.
While I'm on my own, I've
yet to reach the end.
So won't you come along with me right now?
Surely then, WE CAN!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea.
For that treasure known
by everybody as one piece?
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy!
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome!
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon.
The rain will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the anchor.
Now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm.
The storm that you have built within!
Come and have my board at number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up!
We set stuff cause we can't.
Thresh it up, stand tall.
And take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me want to see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams!
Don't think for a second
it's not the truth.
That's the story most will believe?
Not me, come and see!
I am on a journey out to sea.
The world done on my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way!
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done?
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end!
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can!
You can!
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can?
Yes we can! Yes we can!
Here comes the rain rupture!
Oh, no.
It looks like a tidal wave.
Get to high ground.
It'll flood. Run away!
It's right there. We're too late.
Meanwhile, Kinemond and Kanjuro are
climbing the elephant's left leg slowly.
Finally, that accursed shaking has ceased.
I wonder what was the cause.
I dare not wonder.
My only concern is ascending this surface.
Be strong, Nicosiamon!
Do not tarry.
We must make haste before the sun sets.
Perhaps this is too harrowing of a task.
The poor cat.
What do you think?
You're mistaken.
Cats are excellent tree
climbers after all.
A fine point.
Eeeeh! Eeeeh!
Oh!
Water? What?
Oh, that's from a rain rupture
that flooded the country!
He'll be washed away!
Necozymon was created from ink!
I understand that swift
action is necessary,
but what can be done
from such a height? No!
Wow!
That was some rain, huh?
Despite their name, rain
ruptions aren't actually rain.
Twice every day, Zunesha
will bathe itself.
In other words, that was
seawater splashed on its back.
The water passes through a filtration
system at the center of our city,
then is sent through the aqueducts to
become a source of drinking water for?
the whole nation.
Lucky for us, fish come down with
the water too, so we don't have
to worry about food either.
Rain ruptions truly are a blessing.
That's really
something.
What's up, Zohan?
It's the bear guy!
I kind of can't leave the forest right
now, so next time you see the captain,
tell him his crew's here
and he should visit us!
You can't leave?
I'll tell him.
We're counting on you!
That Bo was born here like all of us.
But he's still a pirate, so we
keep a close watch over him.
He's a guest of Cat
Viper, the forest boss.
It's flooding!
There's a shark!
Why is there a shark?
You don't need to be up that high.
We're safe down here.
It's seawater.
The Met wasn't rain just now.
Perhaps the giant elephant
was cleaning its back.
Look at the city.
It was built to accommodate the water.
That's interesting.
The forest, too.
Like the water's a perfect fit.
This flood must be a
regular occurrence, then.
Well, that sounds like a real pain.
This island officially sucks.
Let's find the rest of the crew quick
before we get soaked again you with me
Hey, there's Luffy.
He's at the edge of town the flying
rabbit and the Nami dog lady are with
them They must have tricked him and now
they're taking him to their evil lair.
Stop screaming what's wrong?
Then it's true. They must be
The whole city's soaking wet.
Yes, but it will drain shortly. Huh?
I know he's here.
I've told you, Karoo. He's not.
bring him to me or i'll destroy this
whole country i've never met this person
that you Karoo speak of so ask me all
damn day but there's nothing i can do
what was that guy's name
you said earlier the
one who attacked this
country before i came
it's jack i saw his obituary
in the newspaper a few days ago
after wreaking havoc here he left and
apparently attacked four
navy vessels that were
transporting do flamingo
to impel down he was
able to sink two of them
in the battle but in the
end he was defeated huh
then he was right by
dress rosa one of the
ships he attacked had
an admiral and the former fleet admiral on
board jack certainly seems
to have a screw loose
the article said his body wasn't
recovered he's likely still alive
I'll never forgive that
monster for what he did
I thought this was the
bright flake Why is it foggy?
It's the right flake You think
Zoro's group made it already?
I would hope so.
I gave them directions to our
hidden fortress a little while ago.
Shambles.
Hey, look who it is! Are you okay?
No missing arms or legs?
They didn't eat you, did they?
Be careful, Nami-dog lady.
That's our captain you got there.
You voracious vixen.
I bet you want to gobble him up, huh?
You better give him back
along with the rest of our
friends or I'm going to
make barbecue out of you.
Well, this is a mess.
Whatever your impression is,
it's all wrong. No matter.
We're here, so you'll understand soon.
Look over there, within the fog.
There are guards and a
gate to our fortress.
Are these the invaders?
You gotta look like enemies to me.
None of them meant any harm.
They only went out into the whale
forest because they were lost.
They didn't know they were supposed
to ring the welcoming bell.
Open the gate.
Deliver this message for me.
The Straw Hat Pirates have arrived.
What?
Is that who they are?
Nami!
Luffy and the crew are here!
They made it!
Finally!
Don't go to sleep!
You have to go see the rest of the crew!
They're alive!
Everyone is safe!
They're really here?
Chopper, that's great!
They're at the fortress gate right now!
Huh?
All your friends arrived.
Pleased to hear it.
No, my mistake.
No big deal.
We have very important guests.
They are the friends of our saviors
and should be welcomed as such.
Huh?
We're pleased to have you there for us.
You're welcome here!
What?!
Hey, guys!
Looks like you're ready to party!
This isn't what I had in mind at all!
Crush!
What's Crush mean, anyway? That's funny.
I thought that your race hated us humans.
Race, huh?
That's a label that the ignorant
give to other minx out of fear.
Nothing more.
And what does that mean?
To us, what you, Tia,
call humans are merely monkey
minx who happen to have less hair.
A different look, but
the same race. I see.
So no reason to hate humans
unless we give you one?
Exactly.
We don't judge by one's differences,
but rather by their character.
I hope you deal well, too.
You too!
We full-body minks are certainly
proud of our fur, no doubt about it.
But a lesser mink coat
definitely has its charm as well,
especially because they're rare here.
There they are!
You're right, I see them!
Hey, look!
Nambi and Chopper are here!
And there's not a scratch on them!
Nambi!
I'm happy for your crew!
Crush!
I got caught!
Let me through!
Okay, Crush! Yeah, yeah!
Your crew will finally be together again!
OK, so they don't hate us, but maybe
they like us a little too much.
Goofy! Hey, guys!
Man, I was worried.
I'm so glad you're safe. Nami!
Jumping!
I missed you.
Sorry to keep you waiting, pal.
So Sanji, Brook, and
Momo are here too, huh?
I'm sorry, Sanji's gone.
Would you look at that?
Why, the sun is setting already.
I suppose we'll have to return to the
ship and resume our climb tomorrow.
We did it.
I see you're a man of taste.
Here, have another cup.
I'm happy to share.
We call this monkey wine.
We make plenty thanks to the
abundance of fruits in the forest.
Well, thank you.
It's damn fine stuff.
Enough of the cuddles.
Can't you see I'm drinking here?
Aw, but it's fun.
Let me get a devil, man.
Yeah, let us go, too.
Just one little lick.
That's enough.
You're weirding me out.
Hey, don't be mean, Zoro.
You're giving us all this meat and
you can't be nice for one second.
I hope that our cultural practices
don't give you a bad impression.
Mingship expresses our tribe's
great fondness towards you, Tia.
What kind of meat is this? That's hippo.
This one's lizard, frog, alligator.
We don't eat animals with fur, by the way.
I'm not complaining, but why are
you throwing us this huge party?
A friend of our saviors.
is a friend of ours, too.
Saviors, huh?
They need the whole story.
Hey, Brooke!
Oh, Joy, I read about your big battle.
I'm so glad you're all OK.
I missed you.
What's wrong?
You're all banged up.
Never mind me.
I'm sorry about Sanji.
I feel like I've lost all face.
Not that I have one to begin with.
Oh, hey.
Wasn't Momo supposed to
be with you guys, too?
Yes, and he's unharmed.
But the thing is, he's not very
fond of the makes. Well, why not?
They're so nice to us.
That's true, but he's decided
to lock himself up in a room.
Still, that's convenient for us. Huh?
Could you explain that better?
Because you're not making any sense.
Just come this way, please.
Hey, all newcomers to Zoe, huddle up.
First off, where did Kinemun go?
We got split up, but
he should be here soon.
Well, that's fine.
Yeah, it'll work out nicely.
While we're here, please do not mention
the land of Wano or samurai either.
Better not risk it.
It might cause offense to the minks.
Or pain more accurately.
It might even make them hate you.
Make them hate us?
Okay, but what's the deal?
What's wrong with the samurai?
There's something about this
country you didn't know.
So you thought you could get away.
But you can't run now.
Come here, barren corpse.
What's that for?
A corpse?
Once U-T-O reach right flank, that's
where you'll find your crew's corpse.
We'll find what?
So when she said there was a corpse,
she was just talking about Brooke.
We call him that as a term of endearment.
Kind of misleading, don't you think?
Such a lovely surprise.
I've never seen such an
alluring creature before.
Dog mains can't resist chewing a bone.
What can I say?
Fine, whatever.
Luffy, I don't see Traffy. Is he here?
Yeah, he said Bear Place. He's fine.
Instead, we should worry more about Sanji.
He left you a letter, didn't he?
This thing will work
out one way or another.
Hmm.
He wasn't kidnapped.
He just left.
That's what I'm worried about!
The whole thing is way too fishy!
I'm so sorry. We...
we couldn't do anything to stop him!
Hey, you don't need to cry. Yeah.
I mean, maybe?
Honestly, I don't know if it's
something to cry about or not.
What I'm saying is you need to give us
some more details, because I'm lost.
No kidding.
Last I heard, Big Mom's ship was there.
But I don't know what happened
next or how you guys got away.
Then it's a giant elephant
and talking animal people
and something bad happened
and the city got destroyed.
And I thought the Mink
tribe was our enemy.
But we got here and they all love us.
We're friends of their
saviors, they're telling me.
Listen, Nami.
We need to hear the details in full.
Tell us everything that's
happened in the past 11 days.
since you left Dressrosa aboard the Sunny.
I'm sorry.
This whole situation has me worked up.
Okay, I'll tell you
everything that happened.
First, we ran into trouble when we
were barely off the coast of Dressrosa.
The Big Mom Pirates appeared on
a huge singing ship. Singing?
Shipping, shipping!
We were able to spot
the two members of her
crew that Luthi ran into
back on Fishman Island.
Mama, confirming that
we have located Caesar.
Let us send them on our bon voyage by seeking
their ship to recover Monsieur Caesar.
But they had company.
A fellow member of the worst generation,
Capone gang veggie seems like his
crew is working under Big Mom now?
They came for Caesar,
but it wasn't a rescue.
In fact, he was terrified
Although it's not like we
could escape either way.
So even if it was crazy, we
needed to do something in a hurry!
Let's use a coup de burst to run away!
What about the gout cannon?
We don't have enough spare cola for that.
I got a different plan this time.
Whatever your plan is, hurry up!
If you don't want them to
take you, then play nice!
Okay, Brooke, we're gonna fight him
from the stern and create an opening.
Roger.
Welcome to the Soul Parade!
Chopper Robin, is that really you?
Here he comes. Ready?
I do not approve of this bad one bit!
You will pay for this.
Some audacity treating me like a bag!
Will you stop resisting us?
We're trying to save you.
Thank you, Chopper. Nice bitch.
He can fly?
Here we go.
Well, a prayer!
Spectre!
A room cannibals in our way!
The starbursts take a service, damn it!
My turn, now!
Climb intact!
Weather!
Tag!
Come hatch!
K-Club!
We're going to lose
them! What should we do?
Don't you guys really kick some ass?
That doesn't make me blush at all.
That was on the edge of my seat.
New bird teamwork! You're
so clever. Oh, stop.
I know I'm awesome, but please.
So you came here after that how
long did it take so was close
to us at the time luckily we
made it here the very next day
So we've been here ten days.
I have a question about the city
It looked like the oldest sign of
destruction was from about two weeks ago,
so the incident was over by
the time everyone arrived.
That's correct.
When we found your friends here, most of
our country had already been destroyed.
Despite that,
their arrival was nothing short of a
miracle for our people without their help.
We'd be lost.
We owe them for their courage and
for choppers medical expertise.
Everyone here in the mokumo
dukedom was nearly wiped out.
I know the
wounds are still
pretty fresh on this whole?
So if you don't want to talk
about it, I'm okay with that.
No, we're allies now.
You two need to know.
I will tell you everything
that happened that day.
Hey! Everybody!
The Duke is awake!
I can't believe it!
Finally!
Emily!
Duke Dogstorm, I was so worried.
OK, I'll give him a checkup
and see what he needs.
Tristan, Miyagi, let's go! Whoa!
On my way!
Boy, oh boy!
I have got to see the master at work!
Please, Dr.
Miyagi, wait for me!
Oh, hey, I almost forgot.
Duke Dog Storm said he'd like
to meet with our saviors ASAP.
Right, got it.
Will Yuti and your crew
please come with me?
Okay, whatever.
But who's this dog?
He is the leader of the Mokumo
Dukedom, meaning the ruler of all Zo.
He was hurt badly in the attack, and
unfortunately he's been in a coma ever since.
Same as our other leader.
Huh?
You've got two? Indeed.
It may seem strange, but this is our way.
There is the King of
the Day, Duke Dogstorm.
And the King of the
Night, Master Cat Viper.
Oh, hey, I heard the news.
Nice job beating Doflamingo.
Well, it was really Straw Hat who did it.
Let's catch up back at the base.
This way, Captain.
Sure.
Then, in an instant, it
all came crashing down.
The incident began 17
days ago, to be exact.
A month and a half after
Beppo and his friends arrived,
the visitor spell rang out across
the Mokumo dukedom once more.
Except this time, it
wasn't the welcoming bell.
Rather, it was a sound we
hoped we would never hear.
The raiding bell.
That's not the welcoming bell.
It's the raiding bell.
The what?
A young lady like you,
Karoo, wouldn't know.
It's never been wrong in your lifetime.
A bunch of pirates broke down the gate!
Everybody get ready to fight!
Trampling down the forest on the
way, they invaded our peaceful city.
Feeling such a huge disturbance on
its back, Zunesha let out a roar.
So who were they?
What did they even want from you?
They wanted something that
we could not give to them.
Something we didn't have.
Our pleas fell on deaf ears.
You're hiding a warrior
from the land of Wano here.
Now hand over Race or we will
smash this country to pieces!